A Guide to the Fritz Albert Lipmann papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA123
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Manuscripts and Notes, 1930-1985; 4; 17 Cubic Feet
  - Enzymatic activation of sulfate, 2 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Enzymatic activation of sulfate, 3 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Enzymatic activation of tryptophan analogues (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Enzymatic degradation and resynthesis of CoA (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Enzymatic formation of adenyl tryptophan (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Enzymatic group activation and transfer (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Enzymatic hydrolysis (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Enzymatic mechanism of guanosine, 1 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Enzymatic mechanism of guanosine, 2 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Enzymatic phosphorylation of fish phosvitin (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Enzymatic reaction (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Enzymatic sequence (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Enzymatic studies (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Enzymatic synthesis of adenosine, 1 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Enzymatic synthesis of adenosine, 2 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Enzymatic synthesis of RNA (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Enzymatic transacetylation (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Enzyme-bound phosphopantoteine (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Enzyme "smoker" transcript (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Enzyme of polypeptide synthesis (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Epidural growth factor (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - E. Coli (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - E. Coli adenyl cyclase (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Esterification of ATP, 1 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Esterification of ATP, 2 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Eglina gracilis (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Eukaryotic mRNAs (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - [Evolution manuscript] (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Evolution, 1 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Evolution, 2 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Experiments in hemoglobin biosynthesis (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Experiments with C¹⁴ (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Experiments with reduced cysteine sRNA (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Factors functioning in chain start (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Federation meeting abstracts, 1958 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Federation meeting abstracts, 1959 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Feodor (Fitzi) Lynen, 1911-1979 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Fifty years of ATP (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - First draft on amino acid activation (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - First drafts of vitamin chapter (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Flavoprotein catalyzed pyruvate oxidation (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Flux of energy and its distribution in living organisms (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Formation of a ternary complex (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Formation of a ternary complex between formulatable, 1 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Formation of a ternary complex between formulatable, 1 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Formation of a tryptophan ATP (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Formation of adenosine (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Formation of pyrophosphate (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Fractionation of a non-particulate (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Functional group of CoEnzyme A (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Functions of G and T (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Functions of the elongation factors, 1 of 3 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Functions of the elongation factors, 2 of 3 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Functions of the elongation factors, 2 of 3 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Further studies on bacterial polypeptide elongation (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Fusidic acid stabilization (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - General energy (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Genetic code notes (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Genetic information transfer (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Glucose binding and transport proteins, 1 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Glucose binding and transport proteins, 1 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Glucose binding transport, 1 of 2 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Glucose binding transport, 2 of 2 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Glutathione and protein synthesis (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Glutathione synthesis (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Glycogen synthesis (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Glycogen synthesis from glucose (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Glycogen synthese in muscle (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Gramicidan S and tyrocidine (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Group potential (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - growing peptide chains (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - [GTP] (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - GTP-promoted binding (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Guanosine triphosphate (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Hemoglobin biosynthesis (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Heparitin sulfate (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Hexose phosphates (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Hilz-sulfate paper (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Historical development, 1 of 3 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Historical development, 2 of 3 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Historical development, 3 of 3 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - History of bioenergetics (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Human mind and condition (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Hydrolysis of guanosine (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Hypothalamic release hormones, 1 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Hypothalamic release hormones, 2 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Identification of gluconolactose (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Identification of enzymatically active sulfate (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Identification of y-Glutamylcysteenyl (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Immunochemical distinction (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - In vitro degradation of guanosine 5 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - In vivo and in vitro synthesis of ppGpp (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Inability of E. coli Ribosomes (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Incorporation of C¹⁴ into bacterial peptides (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Incorporation of 5 -Ribosyluracil Triphosphate (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Incorporation of Valine-1-C¹⁴ (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Induction of specific amino acid binding proteins (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Inhibition of mitochondria (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Inhibition of protein synthesis (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Initiation of T4 DNA (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Insulation action on protein synthesis (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Inhibition by the antibiotic fusidic acid (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Inhibition of mitochondria (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Initiation of polyphenylalanine synthesis (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Interaction of eukaryote, 1 of 2 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Interaction of eukaryote, 2 of 2 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Interaction of GTP (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Interrelation between activation and polymerization (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Interrelation between GTPase and amino acid polymerization, 1 of 2 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Interrelation between GTPase and amino acid polymerization, 2 of 2 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Interrelations between polypeptide chain elongation factors (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Interscience publishers guides for authors (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Isolation and development of protein biosynthesis (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Isolation and fractionization of soluble ribonucleic acid (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Isolation and indentification of active sulfate (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Isolation and properties of the E. Coli amino acid (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Isolation and properties of the E. Coli amino acid aceyl transferase system (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Isolation from normal and rous sarcoma virus (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Isolation of a glucose transport system, 1 of 3 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Isolation of a glucose transport system, 2 of 3 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Isolation of a glucose transport system, 3 of 3 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Isolation of a peptidyl-pantetheine protein, 1 of 3 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Isolation of a peptidyl-pantetheine protein, 2 of 3 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Isolation of a peptidyl-pantetheine protein, 3 of 3 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Isolation of a tryptophan (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Isolation of adenosine (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Isolation of adenyl cyclase from E. Coli (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Isolation of amino acid (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Isolation of an enzyme-bound pentadecapeptide, 1 of 3 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Isolation of an enzyme-bound pentadecapeptide, 2 of 3 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Isolation of an enzyme-bound pentadecapeptide, 3 of 3 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Isolation of bacterial chain elongation factors (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Isolation of enzyme-bound peptide, 1 of 2 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Isolation of enzyme-bound peptide, 2 of 2 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Isolation of uracil (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Journal information (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Journal of Biological Chemistry (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Klein material (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Kleinkauf paper (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Kleinkauf paper worksheets (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Kucan charts (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Lactic dehydrogenases (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Les Prix Nobel (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Leucine acceptor (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Leucine acceptors-thesis (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Levels of chloramphenicol sensitivity (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Light-induced oxidation-reduction charges (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Light-induced phosphorylation (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Linear Gramicidin, 1 of 3 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Linear Gramicidin, 2 of 3 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Linear Gramicidin, 3 of 3 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Lipmann symposium (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Manganese ion (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Master copy of book (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Mechanism of citrulline synthesis (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Mechanism of hyrolysis of amino acyl RNA (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Mechanism of polypeptide chain termination of E. Coli (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Mechanism for polypeptide synthesis on a protein template (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Mechanism of activation by adenosine (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Mechanism of sulfate activation and transfer (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Mechanism of sulfurylation of choline (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Medical Research Council (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Membrane diffusion studies (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Membrane transport (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Messenger RNA, 1 of 2 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Messenger RNA, 2 of 2 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Messenger RNA manuscript, 1 of 2 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Messenger RNA manuscript, 2 of 2 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Metabolic function of CoA (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Metabolic function of pantothenic acid (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Metabolism in enzymology (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Metabolism in sulfur compounds (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Metabolism of 3-carbon compounds (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Methods of enzymology, 1 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Methods of enzymology, 2 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Methods, texts, and tables (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Microbial iron transport compounds (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Molecular evolution and protobiology (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Molecular technology, 1 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Molecular technology, 2 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Molecular technology II, 1 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Molecular technology II, 2 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - mRNA (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Multiple forms of leucyl sRNA (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - My Evolution as a Biochemist (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Nachmansohn-Tooze (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Need and use of energy by the organism (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - N-Phosphopuromycin (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - New perspectives in biology (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - NEWS article (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Nobel material (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Non-enzymatic reactions (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Non-participation of RNA (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Non-ribosomal polypeptide, 1 of 3 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Non-ribosomal polypeptide, 2 of 3 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Non-ribosomal polypeptide, 3 of 3 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Non-ribosomal polypeptide synthesis, 1 of 2 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Non-ribosomal polypeptide synthesis, 2 of 2 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Non-ribosomal synthesis (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Notes on E. Coli (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Nucleic acids (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Nucleic acids and the genetic code (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Nucleoside diphosphate of liver mitochondria (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Nucleotide specifity of s stringent factor (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Oak Ridge material, 1952 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Oak Ridge symposium paper, 1 of 2 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Oak Ridge symposium paper, 2 of 2 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - On firm, nonconvalent binding (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - On the ATP-sulfate reaction (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - On the enzymatic mechanism of CoA (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - On the mechanism of acetylation of fetal and chicken hemoglobins, 1 of 2 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - On the mechanism of acetylation of fetal and chicken hemoglobins, 2 of 2 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - On the role of ammonium (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - On the site of esterification of amino acids (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - on the role of soluble ribonucleic acid, 1 of 2 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - on the role of soluble ribonucleic acid, 2 of 2 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Origin of life (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Original of prebiological systems, 1 of 3 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Original of prebiological systems, 2 of 3 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Original of prebiological systems, 3 of 3 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Original drafts of two CoA materials papers (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Oxidative phosphorylation (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Paper of Canada (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Papers-PNAS, 1 of 2 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Papers-PNAS 2 of2 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Pantetheine-linked peptide (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Peptide bond formation (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Peptide bond formation in protein synthesis (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Peptide RNA-Poland papers (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Peptide synthesis and evolution (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Peptidyl transfers (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Phage protein synthesis (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Phenylalanyl puromycin (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Phosphate bonds (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Phosphate bonds II (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Phosphate incorporation into alkaline phosphate of E. Coli (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Phosphoenolpyruvate (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Phospho-enzyme intermediary in acetate kinase action (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Phospho-enzyme intermediary in phosptoglycerate kinase action (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Phosphorylation of alkaline phosphatase (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Phosphorylation of ribosomal protein s6 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Phosphorylation of the Mr 3400 protein (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Phosphotyrosine (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Phosphotyrosine and proteins (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Protophosphorylation and photohyrolysis (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Protophosphorylation in extracts of rhotosprillum rubrum, 1 of 2 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Protophosphorylation in extracts of rhotosprillum rubrum, 2 of 2 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Photosynthetic bacteria (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Polymerator (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Polymerization (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Polyphenylalanene synthesis (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Polypeptide biosynthesis, 1 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Polypeptide biosynthesis, 2 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Polypeptide chain elongation, 1 of 3 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Polypeptide chain elongation, 2 of 3 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Polypeptide chain elongation, 3 of 3 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Polypeptide initiation (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Polypeptide chain termination (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Polypeptide seconds, 1 of 3 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Polypeptide seconds, 2 of 3 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Polypeptide seconds, 3 of 3 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Polypeptide synthesis of gramicidin S (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Polypeptide synthesis with sucrose (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Polypeptide synthesis with sucrose gradient (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Polypeptide synthesis without nucleic acids, 1 of 2 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Polypeptide synthesis without nucleic acids, 2 of 2 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Poly-u effect data (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Possible role of nucleopeptide (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - ppGpp, a signal molecule (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Preparation and properties of sulfuryl adenylates (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Printing information (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Probleme in der Biosynthese (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Production of mitochondrial peptide chain (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Projecting backwards from the present stage of evolution, 1 of 2 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Projecting backwards from the present stage of evolution, 2 of 2 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Protein and RNA synthesis (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Protein chain initiation (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Protein kinase (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Protein paper (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Protein phosphosy (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Protein synthesis, 1 of 3 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Protein synthesis, 2 of 3 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Protein synthesis, 3 of 3 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Protein synthesis and ribonucleic acid, 1 of 2 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Protein synthesis and ribonucleic acid, 2 of 2 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Protein synthesis from aminoacyl-sRNAs (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Protein synthesis in brain slices, 1 of 3 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Protein synthesis in brain slices, 2 of 3 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Protein synthesis in brain slices, 3 of 3 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Protein synthesis in streptococcus faecalis (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Protein synthesis in ribosomal system (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Protein transport (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Pseudomonas hydrophila (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - p32-n-phosphopuromycin (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Purification and properties of guanosine (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Purification of denatured EGF (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Purification of a specific reversible tyr-p-phosphate, 1 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Purification of a specific reversible tyr-p-phosphate, 2 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Purification of the polyenzymes, 1 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Purification of the polyenzymes, 2 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Purification of the polyenzymes responsible for tyrocidine synthesis (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Puromycin (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - RNA-cystine (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Some coding properties of E. coli (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Sulfate reduction by chick yolk sac (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Radioactivity (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Radioactivity AEC applications (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Reaction mechanism of mRNA (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Reaction of ribosome-bound peptidyl sRNA, 1 of 2 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Reaction of ribosome-bound peptidyl sRNA, 2 of 2 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Reactivity of analogues with pancreatic tryptophan-activating enzyme (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Reduced binding of epidermal growth factor (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Reduction of tyrosine-o-sulfate (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Reflections on the evolutionary transition from prokaryotes, 1 of 2 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Reflections on the evolutionary transition from prokaryotes, 2 of 2 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Regulation of prolactin synthesis (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Regulation of the in vivo synthesis of the polypeptides (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Relation between aceton and pyruvic oxide (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Relation between the direction and mechanism of polymerization, 1 of 3 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Relation between the direction and mechanism of polymerization, 2 of 3 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Relation between the direction and mechanism of polymerization, 3 of 3 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Relation between sporulation and the induction of antibiotic synthesis, 1 of 3 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Relation between sporulation and the induction of antibiotic synthesis, 2 of 3 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Relation between sporulation and the induction of antibiotic synthesis, 3 of 3 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Relationship of CoA to lipid synthesis (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Relationship of CoA to lipid synthesis in yeast (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Release of tRNA (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Removal of CTP during ribosome washing (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Repression of in vivo synthesis (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Resolution of the E. coli aminoacyl sRNA transfer (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Reticulocyte hemolysates (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Reticulocytes and E. coli (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Reticulocytes and rat liver (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Reversal of rous sarcoma (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Reversibility of the citrulline phosphorylase reaction (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Reversibility of the pyrophosphoryl transfer (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Reversible phosphate transfer, 1 of 2 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Reversible phosphate transfer, 2 of 2 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Ribosomal and nonribosomal synthesis (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Ribosome (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Ribosomes (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Ribosome dependence (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Ribosome-dependent GTP (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Ribosome-directed protein synthesis (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Ribosome-independent soluble stringent (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Ribosome notes (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Ribosome specifity (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - RNA data (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Rnase hydrolysis (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Role of adenyl cyclase, 1 of 2 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Role of adenyl cyclase, 2 of 2 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Role of divalent ions, 1 of 2 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Role of divalent ions, 2 of 2 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Role of phosphorylation in photosynthesis (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Sarah Ratner's festschrift (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Schism between life and laboratory (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Science paper seconds, 1 of 2 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Science paper seconds, 2 of 2 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Science paper seconds 2 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Scientific creativity (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Search for remnants of early evolution (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Seminars (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Separation of a cyclic 3'5, 1 of 2 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Separation of a cyclic 3'5, 2 of 2 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Separation of cytoplasmic and mitochondrial elongation factors from yeast (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Separation of light and dark reactions in photohydrolysis (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Separation of mitochondrial and cytoplastic peptide, 1 of 2 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Separation of mitochondrial and cytoplastic peptide, 2 of 2 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Separation of steroid sulfokinases, 1 of 2 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Separation of steroid sulfokinases, 2 of 2 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Separation of the two enzymatic phases (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Separation of three microbial amino acid polymerization factors (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Serine hydroxyl (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Slow Beginnings-draft (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Slow Beginnings 2, 1 of 3 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Slow Beginnings 2, 2 of 3 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Slow Beginnings 2, 3 of 3 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Slow Beginnings, 1 of 3 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Slow Beginnings, 2 of 3 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Slow Beginnings, 3 of 3 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Soluble RNA from rat liver (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Some basic biochemical questions (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Some implications of the role of CoA (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Some properties of E. Coli (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Specifity and evolutionary divergence of the antigenic structure (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - sRNA (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - sRNA from E. Coli (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - sRNA isolation procedures (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - sRNA recovery (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - sRNA stability (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Stability of n-ethyl maleimide (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Stepwise reactivation yielding a complex (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Stepwise synthesis of a tripeptide (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Stimulation of amino acid activation (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Stimulation of Galactokinase synthesis in E. Coli (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Stimulatory effect of ammonium (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Structure of CoA (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Studies of the enzymes (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Studies on an oxalacetic carboxylase (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Studies on sulfate activation (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Studies on the ATP-propionate reaction (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Studies on the biosynthesis of valinomycin (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Studies on the initial step of fatty acid activation (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Studies on the interchangeability of one of the mammalian, 1 of 3 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Studies on the interchangeability of one of the mammalian, 2 of 3 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Studies on the interchangeability of one of the mammalian, 3 of 3 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Studies on the synthetic function (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Studies on the turnover and messenger activity (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Study of the threonyladenylate complex, 1 of 2 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Study of the threonyladenylate complex, 2 of 2 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Sulfate activating enzymes (Box 95, Folder 8)